Mariam Mirzoyan

Profile

Front-end Developer with over 3 years of experience working with HTML, CSS, Javascript, React JS, and Git. Ready to work both in a team and independently.

In 2023, I completed the Meta Front-End Developer Professional Certificate course series provided by Coursera, during which I gained relevant experience in different areas of web development such as version control, UI/UX principles, testing, programming paradigms, etc. I used all this knowledge in various assessments and projects, including React websites considering real-world scenarios. I also participated in peer-graded assessments having a chance to see and evaluate other developers' works.

I am looking for an opportunity to work in a professional environment, gain more experience, master new tools, and implement them in real-world projects.

Experience

Wirestock Armenia — Content Reviewer

MARCH 2023 - PRESENT

Check content quality, report stolen content, and edit metadata.

Wirestock Armenia — Keyword Specialist

JULY 2021 - FEBRUARY 2023

Add titles, descriptions, and keywords based on the content.

History Museum of Armenia — Cashier

JANUARY 2019 - JULY 2021

Education and Certificates

Meta Front-End Developer Professional Certificate

Brusov State University — Faculty of Russian and Foreign Languages Linguistics (English)- Bachelor's Program

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Git
- React
- Next.js
- TypeScript
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- Docker
- Redux
- WordPress

Other Skills

- Adobe Photoshop
- Figma

Languages

- English Fluent
- Russian Fluent
- Japanese Basic

Contacts

Phone: 077-39-93-59

Email: marmirzoyan96@gmail.com
Github: https://github.com/Mari3367
Website: https://mari3367.github.io/